# LUCIMARA MACEDO

## JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER



07389 821600



lucimacedom@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/lucimaramacedom



https://github.com/LuciMacedo



Milton Keynes - UK

# EDUCATION

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

HyperionDev Current enrolled

#### **IGNITE-REACT COURSE**

Rocketseat

Sep - 2022

#### WEB GAME DEVELOPER

Digital Innovation One May - 2022

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Gama Academy Jun -2021

#### **DEGREE PHYSICAL EDUCATION**

Dom Bosco University Dec - 2008

# SKILLS

- Python
- Problem-solving
- JavaScript
- Interpersonal Skills
- HTML
- Attention to detail
- CSS
- Self-awareness
- React
- Self-learning
- Git
- Time management
- GitHub

# **OBJECTIVE**

To leverage my knowledge and experience in a dynamic organization that provides robust opportunities for professional growth and development, while utilizing my skills and expertise to contribute to the success of the company.

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A focused, results-driven, and highly capable Junior Software Engineer offering sound theoretical knowledge and practical experience in projects using Python, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Git, and GitHub. Utilizes superior professional abilities to ensure that users can easily interact with the program. A team player who develops communicative working relationships to ensure the smooth running of daily processes

## EXPERIENCE

Please find the selected projects I have developed in my portfolio on the following web links:

- <a href="https://www.lucimacedo.com">https://www.lucimacedo.com</a>
- https://www.hyperiondev.com/portfolio/146288/

## **TEACHER ASSISTENT**

Walnuts School

#### March 2023 - Present

Providing individual or small group assistance to students who need extra help or attention

## **DEPUTY SITE MANAGER**

Fit For Sport

#### Set 2018 - Nov 2020

I was responsible for managing all aspects of running the club and providing a structured environment for children's growth and development. **Key achievement:** One of my key achievements was reducing customer complaints by implementing a new feature on the booking website. This feature made it easy to identify student classrooms and transport them from their classrooms to session locations. As a result of this new feature, I received positive feedback from parents and the School Principal.

## PE TEACHER, SWIMMING TEACHER, AND COORDINATOR

Bom Jesus Educational Group - Brazil

#### Feb 2008 - Feb 2018 (10 yrs)

My responsibilities included managing employees to deliver a safe and effective program and providing effective communication with parents. **Key achievement:** successfully planned and executed a variety of sports events throughout the year with exceptional attention to detail and a focus on providing memorable experiences for participants.

## LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- English